{
    "count": 20,
    "quiz": [
        {
            "question": "What do we call water in its solid form?",
            "ex1": "Shaff",
            "ex2": "Vapor",
            "ex3": "Liquid",
            "ex4": "Ice",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whick group released the hit album 'Backstreet's Back' in 1997?",
            "ex1": "The Backstreet Boys",
            "ex2": "Take That",
            "ex3": "Boyzone",
            "ex4": "East 17",
            "answer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "What organ of a flower produces the pollen?",
            "ex1": "Sepal",
            "ex2": "Carpel",
            "ex3": "Stamen",
            "ex4": "Petal",
            "answer": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you were born on July 1st, what would your astrological sign be?",
            "ex1": "Virgo",
            "ex2": "Aries",
            "ex3": "Cancer",
            "ex4": "Pisces",
            "answer": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is a famous landmark of New York City?",
            "ex1": "Statue of Liberty",
            "ex2": "Sphinx",
            "ex3": "Eiffel Tower",
            "ex4": "Golden Gate Bridge",
            "answer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which branch of physics is concerned with heat and temperature and their relation to energy and work?",
            "ex1": "Fluid mechanics",
            "ex2": "Electrodynamics",
            "ex3": "Plasticity",
            "ex4": "Thermodynamics",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last but not...?",
            "ex1": "Fast",
            "ex2": "Just in time",
            "ex3": "Latest",
            "ex4": "Least",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "When does the big hand of a clock point to the 12?",
            "ex1": "Every quarter to",
            "ex2": "Every half hour",
            "ex3": "Every full hour",
            "ex4": "Every quarter past",
            "answer": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "A pentagon has how many sides?",
            "ex1": "Ten",
            "ex2": "Three",
            "ex3": "Five",
            "ex4": "Seven",
            "answer": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the major landmark in Seattle, Washington, that is 605 feet (184 meters) tall?",
            "ex1": "Space Needle",
            "ex2": "Liberty Lance",
            "ex3": "Sky Stick",
            "ex4": "Peace Pencil",
            "answer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Originally, most early Irish poetry was written in what language?",
            "ex1": "Old English",
            "ex2": "Latin",
            "ex3": "Hebrew",
            "ex4": "Gaelic",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the symbol of Christianity?",
            "ex1": "Square",
            "ex2": "Triangle",
            "ex3": "Circle",
            "ex4": "Cross",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bats are...?",
            "ex1": "Insects",
            "ex2": "Birds",
            "ex3": "Reptiles",
            "ex4": "Mammals",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a baby horse called?",
            "ex1": "Kitten",
            "ex2": "Mule",
            "ex3": "Lamb",
            "ex4": "Foal",
            "answer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "What fruit should be peeled before you eat it?",
            "ex1": "Banana",
            "ex2": "Cherry",
            "ex3": "Grapes",
            "ex4": "Apple",
            "answer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Salvador Dali belonged to which artistic school?",
            "ex1": "Baroque",
            "ex2": "Mannerism",
            "ex3": "Surrealism",
            "ex4": "Romanticism",
            "answer": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which basketball team does Dirk Nowitzki play for?",
            "ex1": "Golden State Warriors",
            "ex2": "Dallas Mavericks",
            "ex3": "Chicago Bulls",
            "ex4": "Miami Heat",
            "answer": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is hit by Ice Hockey players?",
            "ex1": "Puck",
            "ex2": "Chuck",
            "ex3": "Jack",
            "ex4": "Duck",
            "answer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Complete the title of the Elton John No.1 - \"Candle in the...\"?",
            "ex1": "Dark",
            "ex2": "Night",
            "ex3": "Wind",
            "ex4": "Fire",
            "answer": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The brother of my mother is my...?",
            "ex1": "Grandson",
            "ex2": "Uncle",
            "ex3": "Nephew",
            "ex4": "Brother-in-law",
            "answer": "b"
        }
    ]
}